Jester Hairston Collection MS040
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sound recordings unrelated to Jester Hairston, 1910 -- 1989; 1920 -- 1950; MS040.002; 25.2 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Presenting the Gregg Smith Singers: American folk songs, 1961; MS040.002.023.00028; Gregg Smith Singers (Box 23)
  - Preservation Hall Jazz Band, New Orleans, La., vol 1, 1977; MS040.002.023.00029; Preservation Hall Jazz Band (Box 23)
  - The progressive Mr. De Franco, 1958; MS040.002.023.00030; De Franco, Buddy (Box 23)
  - The red back book, 1973; MS040.002.023.00031; Joplin, Scott (Box 23)
  - Requiem, 1966; MS040.002.023.00032; Encino Presbyterian Church Chancel Choir (Box 23)
  - Resolutions, 1974; MS040.002.023.00033; Greer, Mark (Box 23)
  - Resound ye circling hills, 1965; MS040.002.023.00034; Amherst College Glee Club (Box 23)
  - The road not taken, 1981; MS040.002.023.00035; Singing Sergeants (Box 23)
  - The road not taken, 1981; MS040.002.023.00036; Singing Sergeants (Box 23)
  - The Russian Orthodox Requiem, 1975; MS040.002.023.00037; Cappella Russian Male Chorus (Box 23)
  - Sacred concert, 1955; MS040.002.023.00038; A Cappella Choir of Montebello (Box 23)
  - Sacred echoes, 1960; MS040.002.023.00039; Montebello A Cappella Choir (Box 23)
  - Sacred echoes, 1960; MS040.002.023.00040; Montebello A Cappella Choir (Box 23)
  - Salute to Black composers, 1965; MS040.002.023.00041; Angel City/Inglewood Philharmonic Orchestras (Box 23)
  - Salute to Black composers, 1965; MS040.002.023.00042; Angel City/Inglewood Philharmonic Orchestras (Box 23)
    0 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket./
  - The Sanctuary Choir presents de profundis, 1960; MS040.002.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Say amen, somebody: original soundtrack recording and more, 1983; MS040.002.024.00002; Nierenberg, George T. (Box 24)
  - Schubert: trio no. 2 in E flat major, op. 100, 1983; MS040.002.024.00003; The Immaculate Heart Trio (Box 24)
  - Scrapbook, 1957; MS040.002.024.00004; Schumann, Walter (Box 24)
  - Show boat, 1962; MS040.002.024.00005; Kern, Jerome (Box 24)
  - Sights and sounds: Hartford's festival of faith, 1969; MS040.002.024.00006; South Main Baptist Church (Box 24)
  - Sing unto God, 1965; MS040.002.024.00007; Montebello A Cappella Choir (Box 24)
  - Sing unto God, 1965; MS040.002.024.00008; Montebello A Cappella Choir (Box 24)
  - Sing we now of Christmas, 1960; MS040.002.024.00009; Glendora High School Combined Choirs (Box 24)
  - Singin' the blues, 1965; MS040.002.024.00010; King, B. B. (Box 24)
  - The Smithsonian collection of classic jazz, 1973; MS040.002.024.00011; Williams, Martin (Box 24)
    6 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - So tenderly, 1964; MS040.002.024.00012; Gary, John (Box 24)
  - Soft sands, 1960; MS040.002.024.00013; Peterson, Oscar (Box 24)
  - Songs in calypso, 1959; MS040.002.024.00014; Percentie Brothers (Box 24)
  - Songs of Christmas, 1961; MS040.002.024.00015; Inglewood Presbyterian Chancel Choir (Box 24)
  - Songs of free men, spirituals, 1968; MS040.002.024.00016; Robeson, Paul (Box 24)
  - Songs of Ireland, 1958; MS040.002.024.00017; O'Hara, Mary (Box 24)
  - Songs of new nations, 1964; MS040.002.024.00018; De Paur Chorus (Box 24)
  - Songs of praise, 1960; MS040.002.024.00019; Anne Campbell Singers (Box 24)
  - Songs of the Don Cossacks, 1960; MS040.002.024.00020; Don Cossack Choir (Box 24)
  - Songs of the sea, 1957; MS040.002.024.00021; Mills, Alan (Box 24)
  - A song will rise, 1972; MS040.002.024.00022; Peter, Paul and Mary (Box 24)
  - Sounds of '62, 1962; MS040.002.024.00023; Baldwin High School Highlander Choir (Box 24)
  - The sound of music, 1965; MS040.002.024.00024; Rodgers, Richard (Box 24)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket, descriptive booklet, and sleeve included./
  - Sounds of music, 1962; MS040.002.024.00025; 1962 Medford Senior High School A Cappella Choir (Box 24)
  - Sounds of music, 1962; MS040.002.024.00026; McLane High School Mixed Choir and Chamber Orchestra (Box 24)
  - Sounds spectrum, vol. VII for stage band, 1966; MS040.002.024.00027; Satz, Ralph (Box 24)
  - Special lady, 1987; MS040.002.024.00028; J.R. and James (Box 24)
  - Spirit feel, 1967; MS040.002.024.00029; Kellaway, Roger (Box 24)
  - The spirit of Christmas, 1963; MS040.002.024.00030; The Living Strings (Box 24)
  - Spirituals, 1976; MS040.002.024.00031; Anderson, Marian (Box 24)
  - Spring choral concert, 1968; MS040.002.024.00032; High Schools and Junior Colleges of San Diego County (Box 24)
  - St. Louis blues, 1958; MS040.002.024.00033; Kitt, Eartha (Box 24)
  - Streets I have walked, 1963; MS040.002.024.00034; Belafonte, Harry (Box 24)
  - Strolling strings, 1978; MS040.002.024.00035; United States Air Force Band (Box 24)
  - Strolling strings, 1978; MS040.002.024.00036; United States Air Force Band (Box 24)
  - Stronger with each year, 1979; MS040.002.024.00037; Waldowski, Toby and Barb (Box 24)
  - Suddenly it's the Hi-Lo's, 1957; MS040.002.024.00038; The Hi-Lo's (Box 24)
  - Sunday morning at South Main, 1984; MS040.002.024.00039; South Main Baptist Church (Box 24)
  - Sunshine and rainbows, 1984; MS040.002.024.00040; Gassman, Jan and Clark (Box 24)
  - Sweet little Jesus boy, 1975; MS040.002.025.00001; Talley, Dana and Sue (Box 25)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Originally set of two, one disc missing./ Original record jacket included./
  - Swingin' suite, 1960; MS040.002.025.00002; Callendar, Red (Box 25)
  - Texas songster volume 2, 1964; MS040.002.025.00003; Lipscomb, Mance (Box 25)
  - That old time religion, 1960; MS040.002.025.00004; Amen Choir (Box 25)
  - Them cotton pickin' days is over, 1965; MS040.002.025.00005; Cambridge, Godfrey (Box 25)
  - These are the blues, 1968; MS040.002.025.00006; Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 25)
  - This land is your land, 1980; MS040.002.025.00007; Singing Sergeants (Box 25)
  - Thursday's child, 1956; MS040.002.025.00008; Kitt, Eartha (Box 25)
  - A time for singing, 1980; MS040.002.025.00009; Jenson Publications (Box 25)
  - To wish you a merry Christmas, 1958; MS040.002.025.00010; Belafonte, Harry (Box 25)
  - A treasury of golden Christmas songs, 1963; MS040.002.025.00011; Caravans (Box 25)
  - A treasury of golden Christmas songs, 1963; MS040.002.025.00012; Caravans (Box 25)
  - The Tweed family singers... on tour, 1965; MS040.002.025.00013; Tweed Family Singers (Box 25)
  - Two sides of the Airmen of Note, 1965; MS040.002.025.00014; Airmen of Note (Box 25)
  - The United States Air Force Symphony Orchestra invites you to an evening of beautiful music, 1977; MS040.002.025.00015; United States Air Force Symphony Orchestra (Box 25)
  - University of Southern California Chamber Singers, 1970; MS040.002.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - University of Southern California Concert Choir in spring concert, 1966; MS040.002.025.00017; University of Southern California Concert Choir (Box 25)
  - Up with Donald Byrd, 1964; MS040.002.025.00018; Byrd, Donald (Box 25)
  - Up with people, sing-out musical, 1965; MS040.002.025.00019; Colwell, Ralph (Box 25)
  - Up with people! in Hollywood, 1966; MS040.002.025.00020; Colwell, Ralph (Box 25)
  - Virtuoso!, 1970; MS040.002.025.00021; Roger Wagner Chorale (Box 25)
  - The voice of Negro America, 1970; MS040.002.025.00022; Holy Child Singers (Box 25)
  - The voices of Christmas, 1955; MS040.002.025.00023; Schumann, Walter (Box 25)
  - Wartburg College Choir tour, 1970; MS040.002.025.00024; Wartburg Choir (Box 25)
  - We sing praises, 1983; MS040.002.025.00025; Crouch, Sandra (Box 25)
  - We sing praises, 1983; MS040.002.025.00026; Crouch, Sandra (Box 25)
  - The Weavers at Carnegie Hall, 1956; MS040.002.025.00027; Weavers (Box 25)
  - West Badin Concert Choir: dedicated to memories, 1984; MS040.002.025.00028; West Badin Concert Choir (Box 25)
  - West side story, 1961; MS040.002.025.00029; Bernstein, Leonard (Box 25)
  - West Virginia Wesleyan tour choir 1975-76, 1976; MS040.002.025.00030; West Virginia Wesleyan Tour Choir (Box 25)
  - The western film world of Dimitri Tiomkin, 1981; MS040.002.025.00031; John McCarthy Singers (Box 25)
  - What wondrous love, 1960; MS040.002.025.00032; Robert Shaw Chorale (Box 25)
  - Wheel in a wheel, 1970; MS040.002.025.00033; King's Heralds Quartet (Box 25)
  - White spirituals, 1961; MS040.002.025.00034; Lomax, Alan (Box 25)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket, sleeve, and descriptive booklet included./
  - Wild Tchoupitoulas, 1976; MS040.002.025.00035 (Box 25)
  - The William Hall Chorale concert-adventure tour, China, 1983-07; MS040.002.025.00036; William Hall Chorale (Box 25)
    2 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and additional materials included./
  - Worthy is the lamb, 1979; MS040.002.025.00037; Sanctuary Choir of First Baptist Church, Dallas, Texas (Box 25)
  - Yankee doodle dandies, 1976; MS040.002.025.00038; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 25)
  - Yankee doodle dandies, 1976; MS040.002.025.00039; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 25)
  - Ye are not of the flesh, 1976; MS040.002.025.00040; Henry Sibley High School Choirs (Box 25)
  - You and me, Lord, 1970; MS040.002.025.00041; Smith, Howlett (Box 25)
  - Young peoples' forum '60, 1960; MS040.002.025.00042; Church of Christ, Porterville (Box 25)
  - Young peoples' forum '61, 1961; MS040.002.025.00043; Church of Christ, Porterville (Box 25)
  - Zydeco, Cajun/Creole/Bayou music, 1976; MS040.002.025.00044; Queen Ida and the Bon Temps Band (Box 25)
  - American spirituals [record album], 1950; MS040.002.026.00001; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 26)
    Chicago, IL./ Sonora./ This record album originally contained four records that were produced as part of 'American Spirituals'. However, not all of the records contained in this album at the time of processing were part of the original set. They were likely added to the album for storage purposes.
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.029.00006 MS040.002.029.00007 MS040.002.029.00013 MS040.002.029.00004 MS040.002.029.00005 MS040.002.034.00003 MS040.002.034.00004
  - American spirituals [record album], 1950; MS040.002.026.00002; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 26)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.032.00015 MS040.002.026.00002
  - Jungle drums [record album], 1949; MS040.002.026.00003; Knudson, Thurston (Box 26)
    [New York]./ Decca./ This record album originally contained three records that were produced as part of 'Jungle Drums'. However, not all of the records contained in this album at the time of processing were part of the original set. They were likely added to the album for storage purposes.
    This album originally contained the following MS040.002.029.00009 MS040.002.032.00008 MS040.002.032.00016records:
  - Sistine choir [record album], 1950; MS040.002.026.00004; Capella Sistina [Sistine Chapel Choir] (Box 26)
    Los Angeles, CA./ Sunset Records./ This record album originally contained four records that were produced as part of 'Sistine Choir'. However, not all of the records contained in this album at the time of processing were part of the original set. They were likely added to the album for storage purposes.
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00002 MS040.002.029.00005 MS040.002.033.00002 MS040.002.033.00017
  - West Indian folk songs [record album], 1941 -- 1945; MS040.002.026.00005; Manning, Sam; Felix Krazy Cats (Box 26)
    [United States]./ Decca./ This record album originally contained three records that were produced as part of 'West Indian folk songs'. However, not all of the records contained in this album at the time of processing were part of the original set. They were likely added to the album for storage purposes.
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.030.00003 MS040.002.032.00010 MS040.002.033.00012
  - Untitled record album 001, 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.026.00006 (Box 26)
    This date is approximate and refers to the range of years when this record album was likely manufactured. This record album was commercially produced as generic storage for 10-inch, 78rpm records, which were often sold without jackets. This album originally contained an assortment of records, which may or may not have been arranged by Jester Hairston.
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.029.00019 MS040.002.030.00014 MS040.002.031.00001 MS040.002.031.00012 MS040.002.031.00015 MS040.002.034.00002
  - Untitled record album 002, 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.026.00007 (Box 26)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00009 MS040.002.029.00018 MS040.002.030.00007 MS040.002.030.00012 MS040.002.034.00006
  - Untitled record album 003, 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.026.00008 (Box 26)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00008 MS040.002.028.00016 MS040.002.029.00014 MS040.002.029.00015 MS040.002.029.00021 MS040.002.030.00013 MS040.002.030.00017 MS040.002.030.00018 MS040.002.032.00002 MS040.002.032.00004 MS040.002.032.00006 MS040.002.032.00014 MS040.002.033.00006 MS040.002.033.00007 MS040.002.033.00008 MS040.002.034.00001 MS040.002.034.00008
  - Untitled record album 004, 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.026.00009 (Box 26)
    This date is approximate and refers to the range of years when this record album was likely manufactured. This record album was commercially produced as generic storage for 10-inch, 78rpm records, which were often sold without jackets. This album was originally empty.
  - Classical - vocal [record album], 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.027.00001 (Box 27)
    This date is approximate and refers to the range of years when this record album was likely manufactured. This record album was commercially produced as generic storage for 10-inch, 78rpm records, which were often sold without jackets. The title of this album refers to a handwritten label on the spine of the album, added by Jester Hairston. This album originally contained an assortment of records, which may or may not reflect the original order imposed by Hairston.
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00001 MS040.002.029.00016 MS040.002.029.00017 MS040.002.030.00001 MS040.002.030.00011 MS040.002.027.00001 MS040.002.031.00010 MS040.002.031.00011 MS040.002.031.00013 MS040.002.032.00007
  - Collectors (miscellaneous) [record album], 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.027.00002 (Box 27)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00020 MS040.002.029.00008 MS040.002.029.00011 MS040.002.030.00016 MS040.002.031.00014
  - Collectors (miscellaneous) [record album], 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.027.00003 (Box 27)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00017 MS040.002.029.00010 MS040.002.029.00012 MS040.002.029.00020 MS040.002.030.00009 MS040.002.030.00021 MS040.002.031.00017 MS040.002.033.00011 MS040.002.033.00014
  - Collector's - vocal [record album], 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.027.00004 (Box 27)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00003 MS040.002.028.00004 MS040.002.028.00015 MS040.002.031.00006 MS040.002.027.00008 MS040.002.027.00004 MS040.002.032.00017
  - Popular - instrumental [record album], 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.027.00005 (Box 27)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00007 MS040.002.028.00014 MS040.002.028.00018 MS040.002.028.00019 MS040.002.029.00001 MS040.002.030.00008 MS040.002.032.00001 MS040.002.032.00003 MS040.002.032.00011 MS040.002.033.00010 MS040.002.033.00015
  - Popular - vocal [record album], 1945 -- 1965; MS040.002.027.00006 (Box 27)
    This album originally contained the following records: MS040.002.028.00005 MS040.002.029.00002 MS040.002.030.00022 MS040.002.031.00007 MS040.002.032.00005 MS040.002.032.00009 MS040.002.033.00002 MS040.002.033.00013 MS040.002.033.00018 MS040.002.033.00019 MS040.002.033.00020
  - Adelaide [sides 3 and 4], 1939; MS040.002.028.00001; Hayes, Roland (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Columbia 17175 D (78A)./ Record from album: Classical - vocal, MS040.002.027.00001./
  - Adeste Fidelis / Haec Dies, 1950; MS040.002.028.00002; Capella Sistina [Sistine Chapel Choir] (Box 28)
    Los Angeles, CA./ Sunset Records./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: Sistine choir, MS040.002.026.00004./
  - After you've gone / I'm glad I can make you cry, 1918; MS040.002.028.00003; Burr, Henry; Davis, Marion (Box 28)
    Camden, NJ./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Victor catalog no. 18509./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./
  - All alone / It's all the same to me, 1930; MS040.002.028.00004; Edwards, Cliff [Ukelele Ike] (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Pathe [Path]./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress no. Path 025124 (78A)./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./
  - All night long / I'm going back, back to memphis, Tennessee, 1913; MS040.002.028.00005; Collins, Arthur; Ada Jones Quartette (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress no. Columbia A 1297 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Alone and motherless / Since I met Jesus, 1950; MS040.002.028.00006; Five Blind Boys of Alabama [Happyland Singers] (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Specialty no. 870./
  - Always / Dinah, 1920; MS040.002.028.00007; Crawford, Jesse (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20000 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Am I blue? / Birmingham Bertha, 1929; MS040.002.028.00008; Waters, Ethel (Box 28)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 1837 D (78A)./ From the Warner Brothers talking picture 'On With The Show'./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - And then I prayed / Somebody higher than you and me, 1951; MS040.002.028.00009; Ink Spots (Box 28)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Decca Shelf no. 27494./ Record from album: Untitled record album 002, MS040.002.026.00007./
  - Any day now / Jesus, I'll never forget, 1954; MS040.002.028.00010; Soul Stirrers (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Specialty Shelf no. 868./
  - Atom and evil / Shadrack, 1947; MS040.002.028.00011; Golden Gate Quartette (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 37236 (78A)./
  - Battle hymn of the republic / To you and your lady, 1950; MS040.002.028.00012; Thomas, Buell (Box 28)
    Los Angeles, CA./ Dalton./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - Beans and cornbread / Chicky-mo Craney Crow, 1949; MS040.002.028.00013; Louis Jordan and his Tympany Five (Box 28)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Decca 24673 (78A)./
  - Begin the beguine / Hand to mouth boogie [sides 7 and 8 of 8], 1946; MS040.002.028.00014; Adler, Larry; John Kirby and his Orchestra (Box 28)
    New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Decca 23319 (78A)./ 'Begin the beguine' featured in Warner Brother's picture 'Night and Day'./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Black cat moan / Strugglin' woman's blues, 1927; MS040.002.028.00015; Clara Smith and her Five Black Kittens (Box 28)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 14240 D (78A)./ Record from album: Collector's - vocal, MS040.002.027.00004./ This record is slightly damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Bleeding heart blues / Midnight blues, 1923; MS040.002.028.00016; Smith, Bessie (Box 28)
    New York./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 3936 (78A)./ Record from album: Untitled record album 003, MS040.002.026.00008./
  - Bluin' the blues - foxtrot / Sensation rag - one step, 1918; MS040.002.028.00017; Original Dixieland Jazz Band (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 18483 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./
  - Boogie woogie / On the sunny side of the street, 1939; MS040.002.028.00018; Tommy Dorsey and his orchestra (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Victor./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Victor 20-2005 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Boogie woogie boy / Tiger rag, 1945; MS040.002.028.00019; "Porky'' Freeman Trio (Box 28)
    [United States]./ ARA./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. ARA 133 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Brother low down / Unexpectedly, 1921; MS040.002.028.00020; Williams, Bert (Box 28)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia A 3508 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00002./
  - Carmen - Gypsy dance / La Vigen de la Macarena, 1935; MS040.002.029.00001; Mendez, Rafael (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Coast./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Coast 7038 (78A)./ Record from album: Popular - instrumental, MS040.002.027.00005./
  - Chiming bells of long ago / Sweet and low, 1922; MS040.002.029.00002; Lucy Gates and her male quartette (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Columbia Shelf no. A 3749./ Record from album: Popular - vocal, MS040.002.027.00006./
  - Christmas at mission Santa Barbara, 1935; MS040.002.029.00003; Padre Choristers (Box 29)
    New York./ RCA Custom Records./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Christmas Carols [record jacket only], 1950; MS040.002.029.00004; Columbus Boychoir (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket./
  - Christus / Exalte Justi, 1950; MS040.002.029.00005; Capella Sistina [Sistine Chapel Choir] (Box 29)
  - City called Heaven / Hold on, 1946; MS040.002.029.00006; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 29)
    France./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Record from album: American spirituals, MS040.002.026.00001./
  - City called Heaven / There's a man goin' roun' takin' names [and] Joshua fit the battle of Jericho, 1946 -- 1950; MS040.002.029.00007; Spencer, Kenneth (Box 29)
    Chicago, IL./ Sonora./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Sonora no. 478./ Record from album: American spirituals, MS040.002.026.00001./
  - Cold in hand blues / You've been a good ole wagon, 1925; MS040.002.029.00008; Smith, Bessie (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Columbia 35672 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00002./
  - Conga kongo / Te Moana [sides 1 and 2], 1941; MS040.002.029.00009; Thurston Knudson-Augie Goupil and their Jungle Rhythmists (Box 29)
    [United States]./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Decca 18130 (78A)./ Record from album: Jungle drums, MS040.002.026.00003./ This record is damaged and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Construction gang / A to Z blues, 1924; MS040.002.029.00010; Butterbeans and Susie (Box 29)
    New York./ Okeh./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress Shelf no. Okeh 8163 (78A)./ Record from album: Collectors (miscellaneous), MS040.002.027.00003./